damngeeky.com 2018-07-17

# Privacy Policy - DamnGeeky

Your privacy is one of our foremost concerns and this privacy policy covers all the different ways in which DamnGeeky collects and makes use of your personal information. We make it a point to protect your personal information and make sure that our services offer safe and risk-free environment for you as a user of the website. This privacy policy can be updated any time without prior notice as we reserve the rights to do so, so make it a point to read it carefully before proceeding ahead with using our services. If you don’t accept these privacy policies, please don’t use our website or services. Your use of our DamnGeeky website indicates you have read and understood this privacy policy and indicates your agreement to abide by the Terms of Use in effect.

**Personal information we may collection about you**

DamnGeeky may collect information about your use of our website like the IP Address, worldwide geographical location, internet browsing details, the site which referred you to us, the duration of your stay on our website and the webpages viewed on our site. Apart from this we collect personal information like names, addresses and emails that have been provided by you on voluntary basis in the contact forms, newsletter subscriptions, and comments section.

**User of personal information**

DamnGeeky doesn’t in any way sell or share your private information with any third-party. Neither do we send spam mails or any other information collected by us regarding you. The aggregated information that we collect is used to improve content & design of the website, and only to verify the claims of traffic to the site. Other than that the information is only used to fulfill your requests and communicate with you. Your information is shared with third parties only with your permission, except in response to legal process.

**Processing of personal data**

If you have provided your email address, for example, to receive a newsletter, it can be used to inform you about relevant and interesting news, new products, and offers featured at DamnGeeky. If you do not wish to receive our newsletters, you can unsubscribe at any time.

**Browsing history and IP address**

General visitor data is recorded on DamnGeeky with the aim of optimizing the layout of the website. This data can also be used to put targeted information on the website. To do so, DamnGeeky can also use the IP address of your computer. The IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet. They can be used to predict your geographical location and prepare analysis and reports.

**External links and cookies**

DamnGeeky contains links to external websites and we are not responsible for privacy policies adhered by those websites and nor are we responsible for any tracking methods used by them. We advise you to carefully go through the privacy policies of such websites that collect personally identifiable information.

Cookies are parcels of text sent by a server to a web client (usually a browser) and then sent back unchanged by the client each time it accesses that server. Every time the user visits the webpage, cookies can be used to help identify them. DamnGeeky doesn’t track your cookies or collect any personal information in that way.

**Why cookies?**

[Cookies](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie) are a small piece of data sent from a website and stored in your web browser while you browse that website. Cookies immediately swing into action as soon as you load the website and send the cookies back to the server to notify your previous activity. These are useful techniques to collect and use information to ensure effortless log-in user experience, location and language settings on a website. Also, a cookie helps the website owners how often their sites and pages are viewed by visitors. Furthermore, some cookies make it possible to track your surfing habits, by virtue of which sites and advertisers get to know about your preferences so they can show you more relevant ads.

Cookies are stored on your computer and you can remove them at any time. Remember that once you delete cookies from a website, you will need to log in or set all preferences all over again.

**Advertisers**

DamnGeeky uses third-party advertising on its website, these companies may use your information excluding your name, address, email address or telephone number. The information like demographic detail, geographical location, etc., will only be used to provide relevant advertisements about products and services of your interest.
